<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>DigitalSkills</title>
    
    
    <description>Dedicated to proliferating the knowledge and use of Fundamental Digital Skills.</description>
    
    <link></link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>How to buy second-hand laptops online, for cheap! ($100-$400)</title>
        <description>
          I bought one for $70 while making this post. - 
          I’ve never had much money, but I love computers, so I’ve gotten a bit of practice shopping for used computers online. The purpose of this guide When I started to create DigitalSkills.Info, the idea was to creating all the guides one would need to start learning digital skills to begin...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>/2020-12-18-buy-used-laptop-100-400-dollars/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2020-12-18-buy-used-laptop-100-400-dollars/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Advanced Web Search - Curated List - Google and Beyond</title>
        <description>
          Search Operators, URL Parameters, Order of Operations and More - 
          This curated list is part of a demonstration created as a part of How I use Google to Learn New or Difficult Subjects: Collect and Organize Search Results for your own Benefit, and Share your Findings to get Digital Clout. Google Search This first section includes links and information straight...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>/2020-11-17-advanced-web-search-curated/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2020-11-17-advanced-web-search-curated/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How I use Google to Learn New or Difficult Subjects</title>
        <description>
          Collect and organize search results for your own benefit, share your findings, and get clout - 
          The most powerful skill I’ve developed is using Google Search to learn difficult subjects, discovering much more information than I can find anywhere else. I’ve been meaning to write and learn more about the subject of searching the web, for a while. Once I came up with the idea of...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>/2020-11-14-google-search-learning-new-difficult-subjects/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2020-11-14-google-search-learning-new-difficult-subjects/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Digital Skills Info</title>
        <description>
          A Not-For-Profit Educational Organization - 
          Digital transformation is a popular buzzword used to describe the practices that corporations and government bodies, around the world, use seeking to remain relevant in the digital age. The leaders in legacy institutions know that you have the power to displace their empires from your living room, and are spending...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2020-10-18-digital-transformation-for-the-rest-of-us/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2020-10-18-digital-transformation-for-the-rest-of-us/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
